-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
--------------------------
cece&飞飞，爱的字幕
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: 西西
组长：cece
成员：cece&飞飞
-==…… (*^__^*) ……==-
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第一季 第二十集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 01 Episode 20
孩子们
Kids,
大约在Lily阿姨和Marshall叔叔
订婚八个月的时候
about eight months into Aunt Lily
and Uncle Marshall's engagement,
发生了件紧急情况
there occurred a game-changing emergency.
Van Smoot现在可以预定
Van Smoot is available.
噢, 我的上帝!
Oh,my god!
Van Smoot是位于哈得孙河上的很棒的公寓
Van Smoot house was a gorgeous
mansion right on the Hudson River.
它可以满足Marshall和Lily婚礼所有的需求
It had everything Marshall and
Lily wanted for their wedding,
但它从来没有空置
but it was never available.
然后, 突然, 可以预定了
And then,suddenly,it was.
两个月后有一个预定被取消了
There was a cancellation two months from now.
你想在两个月内举行婚礼?
You want to have our wedding in two months?
不 这不可能
No. It's impossible.
是Van Smoot, Lily
It's Van Smoot,Lily.
这是我们的梦!
It's the dream!
不, 没有足够的时间
No,there's just not enough time.
没有可能...
There's no way...
迷你呕吐
Mini-vomit.
好吧, 听着, 听着
Okay,look,look,look.
我知道这太突然了
I know that it's sudden,
但想想 如果我们不把握机会
but check it.If we don't take this,
猜谁会去交定金
guess who's on their way with a deposit check.
Todd和Valerie?
Todd and Valerie?
当你计划婚礼时
When you're planning a wedding,
总有一对品味相近的新人走快你一步
there's always one couple with similar taste
that seems to be one step ahead of you.
Todd和Valerie就是
Todd and Valerie were that couple.
我们得做决定
We got to make a decision.
Todd和Valerie开始行动了
Todd and Valerie are in motion.
Van Smoot!
孩子们, 注意色彩!
Kids,color!
加油, 宝贝
Come on,baby.
加油, 加油
Come on,come on,come on.
好啊, Marshall
hello,Marshall.
Lily
Lily.
Todd
Todd.
Valerie
Valerie.
楼梯
Stairs.
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我们定到了Van Smoot公寓
We got Van Smoot house.
开始了
It is on.
拉开序幕!
It is on!
就象前苏联共和国阿塞拜疆
Like the Former Soviet Republic of Azerbaijan.
- 什么?
- 你是个奇迹
- What?
- You're a wonder.
你们两个月内就要举行婚礼了
You guys are getting married in two months.
要怎么把一切办妥?
How are you going to get everything done?
分工
Division of labor.
每个人都有任务
Everyone's got a job to do,
听好
so listen up.
Robin, 你和Ted去定花
Okay,Robin,you and Ted go to the florist.
Robin一直生我气自从那晚
Robin had been mad at me since the night
我轻微的夸大了我"没有女朋友"
I slightly exaggerated my not-having
-a-girlfriend-ness.
那是...?
Was it...?
是你女朋友
It was your girlfriend.
你可能想给她回电
You might want to call her back.
或者, 事实上
Or,actually,
Robin, 你去联系花商?
Robin,why don't you go to the florist?
然后,Ted
And,Ted,
我可以利用你建筑上敏锐的眼光...
I could use your keen architectural eye on...
来整理邀请函
on the invitations.
哇,这真是尴尬啊, Lil
Wow,That was really awkward,Lil.
仍然
And still.
现在气氛仍然很尴尬
It's still really awkward right now.
嘿, 那我呢?
Hey,what about me?
我的工作是什么?
What's my job?
我要做什么?
What do I get to do?
好吧, 你的工作很简单
Okay,your job is very simple.
在婚礼上
At the wedding,
不要和任何与我沾亲的人睡觉
do not sleep with anyone even remotely related to me.
Lil, 你知道我不能保证这个
Lil,you know I can't promise that.
看她多可爱
Look how cute she looks.
累坏了
All tuckered out.
嘿, 宝贝
Hey,babe.
嘿, 小家伙
Hey,little one.
嘿, 百合花瓣
Hey,little sparrow.
糟糕!
Crap!
乐队!
Band!
我们忘了乐队!
We forgot a band!
没有乐队的婚礼
只听到大家吃东西的声音
It's just gonna be silence and
then people chewing.
宝贝, 别担心
Baby,don't worry about it.
我找了88乐队!
I called the 88!
谁?
Who?
88乐队
The 88.
一个很棒的乐队
They're this awesome band.
他们在我法律评论派对上表演过
They played my law review party.
他们在摇滚
They were found guilty.
三项审判上有罪
On three counts of rocking.
我两个月前在我表亲Bonzo的婚礼上见过他们
I saw them two months ago at my cousin Bonzo's wedding,
他们不错
they were great.
Led Zeppelin乐队的John "Bonzo" Bonham?
(著名重金属摇滚乐队)
John "bonzo" bonham from Led Zeppelin?
是的, Lily, 我的表亲
Yes,Lily,my cousin,
Led Zeppelin的鼓手
the drummer from Led Zeppelin,
1980去世的那个
who died in 1980,
两个月前结婚了
got married two months ago.
听着, 我...
Look,I...
不能请一个从来没见过的乐队
I can't sign off on a band I've never even seen.
我们甚至不知道他们能不能演奏我们的歌
We... we don't even know if they can play our song.
他们得先过来面试
They're... they're going to have to come over here and audition.
宝贝, 88乐队不面试
Baby,the 88 don't audition.
他们就像婚礼乐队之王
They're,like,the wiggles of wedding bands.
那...
then...
我不干
I have to say no.
宝贝, 他们只在周一前接受预约
Baby,they're only holding the date until Monday.
他们这周会在哪演出吗?
are they playing anywhere this weekend?
我去查查他们的网站
Let me check their website.
怎么?
What?
Lily, 你对乐队的事有点紧张了
Lily,you're being a wee bit intense
about this band thing.
紧张?
Intense?
我要在九周内准备一个200人参加的婚礼
I have a wedding to plan in nine weeks for 200 people.
就算是恐龙也会被我头撞飞
Even if a dinosaur should poke his head out of my butt
然后撞烂咖啡桌
and consume this coffee table,
你得全力支持我, 好不?
I need you to roll with it,okay?
伙计们!
Guys!
我刚尝到了很棒的包办伙食
I just tasted an amazing caterer.
我们有伙食承办人了
We already have a caterer.
噢, 对了 你要结婚了
Oh,right.You're getting married.
你看我干的?
You see what I did there?
拿个...
Took A...
88乐队明天要在新泽西一个高中毕业舞会上演出
it looks like the 88 are playing at a high school prom in New Jersey tomorrow.
毕业舞会?
A prom?
我们可以去吗?
Can... can we go to that?
我们给那个高中打个电话
we'll just call the high school,
他们会让我们站在后面看的
they'll let us stand in the back and watch.
[11秒后]
耶，不, 他们不干
Yeah,no,they won't.
为什么不行?
Why not?
因为我们不是高中生
Cause it turns out we're not in high school.
别担心, 我们可以溜进去
No sweat,we'll just sneak in.
我们不会溜进高中毕业舞会
We're not sneaking in to a high school prom.
不, 我们会
Yes,we are.
这是唯一的办法了
It's the only way.
你要用Barney的主意吗?
You're getting on board with Barney's idea?
天, 你真太着急了
Man,you really have snapped.
离婚礼只有九周了
It's nine weeks till the wedding.
基于这点
At this point,
我会对任何事说yes
I'd say yes to just about anything.
不, Barney
no,Barney.
所以Lily阿姨开始计划溜进毕业舞会
And so, Aunt Lily hatched the plan to crash a prom,
我和你一起
I'll go with you.
真的吗?
Really?
我从来没去过我的毕业舞会
I never got to go to my prom.
春天总有国家曲棍球比赛
We always had field hockey nationals
in the spring.
女同性恋
lesbian.
咳嗽应该掩盖住"女同性恋"
The cough is supposed to cover the "lesbian."
不, 我在尝试和咳嗽分开来的新方法
No,I'm trying to start a thing where the cough is separate.
你们觉得我们看起来够年轻溜进高中吗?
Do you think we look young enough
to blend in at a high school?
拜托, 我永远不会变老
Please,I'm ageless,
Scherbotsky只是需要充足的睡眠
Scherbotsky just needs a good night's sleep,
你的身材还是凹凸有致
and you've got "statutory" written all over your body.
嘿, 为什么不我们都去?
Hey,why don't we all go?
不知道
I don't know
人多可能不好溜进去
more people might be harder to sneak in.
我们可不想把Lily的事情搞砸
We don't want to mess things up for Lily.
耶, 你是对的
Yeah,you're right.
另外, 我和Marshall计划
Besides,Marshall and I have been planning
婚礼前的男士单身之夜
on having a guy's night out before the wedding.
为什么不干脆明晚呢?
Why don't we just make it tomorrow night?
听起来很棒
Sounds awesome.
我们怪异的出去
We should go out and just get freakin' weird.
因为, 你知道, 你是坏人
Cause,you know,you be a bad,bad man,
我是罪犯
and I be an outlaw.
怎样?
What?
嘿, Thelma, Louise
Hey,Thelma,Louise,
你们别太越过界了, 听到没?
y'all don't drive off no cliffs now,ya hear?
糟糕!
Lame!
但说正经的
But seriously,
给我留言
leave me a message,
我稍后去找你们
and we'll meet up later.
好了, 你觉得怎么样?
All right,what do you think?
恐怖
Horrible.
真是个不错的父亲
You're gonna make such a great dad.
你们看起来很古典
You look so classy and nice.
你们这样去肯定立马被认出来
You're going to stick out like a sore thumb.
你们有见过现在孩子们怎么打扮吗
Have you seen how the kids are dressing
these days,
看看阿什莉・辛普森, 林赛罗韩和帕里斯・希尔顿?（都是It Girl）
with the Ashlee and the Lindsay and the Paris?
都穿的像脱衣舞女郎
They all dress like strippers.
现在是变浪荡还是被赶回家
It's go whore or go home.
恩, 我们必需得进去
Well,we have to get in.
我得去看那个乐队
I have to see this band,
因为我们周一前得做决定
cause we have to make a decision by Monday,
因为我71天内就要结婚了
cause I'm getting married in 71 days,
但我们还没有...
and we still don't have...
甜心, 一次只顾一件事, 好吗?
Sweetie,just focus on one thing at a time,okay?
现在, 你只要打扮的像妓女就行了
Right now,you just have to dress like
a whore and that's it.
好的
All right.
这就是精髓
That's the spirit.
现在, 女士们, 放浪起来!
Now,ladies,slut up!
我从没想过这会坏事
I never thought this would be a bad thing,
但我的衣橱就是不够放浪
but my wardrobe just isn't slutty enough.
我都不知道我还有这件衣服
I didn't know I still had this.
什么?
What?
我在毕业舞会上穿的礼服
The dress I wore to my actual prom.
天那, 你是这舞会上最美的女孩
Dude,you are the hottest girl at this prom,
不是一般的美
and not like in a corporate,plastic way.
是真的真的很美
Like,truly,truly hot.
像美丽的灵魂
Like a hot soul.
啊, 你看起来也不错, Scooter
Aw,you look great,too,Scooter.
有个好消息
So big news.
裁判学校来的消息
I heard from umpire school.
我被录取了!
I'm in!
噢, disco!
Oh,disco!
我真为你开心
I am so happy for you.
你是想说为我们两开心, 是不, 宝贝?
You mean happy for us,right,babe?
Scooter, 你会成为裁判的
Scooter,you're gonna be an umpire someday.
不, 宝贝
No,baby.
我们将成为裁判的
We're gonna be an umpire someday.
不错
Nice.
你们看起来很不错
You ladies look good,
但你们的行头还差样东西
but your outfits are missing just one thing.
别, Barney
No,Barney,
这是我们的极限了
this is as far as we're going to go.
我不会再露...
I'm not showing anymore...
两朵美丽的花配上两个如花似玉的人
two beautiful flowers for two beautiful flowers.
真好
Sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
噢, Robin, 你哭了吗?
oh,Robin,are you tearing up?
没有
No.
我从来没参加过毕业舞会, 好不?
I've never been to prom before,okay?
我们得走了 回头见
We got to go.See ya.
拜, 玩的开心
Bye,have fun.
回头见
See you.
她们长大的真快, Ted?
They grow up into skanks so fast,
don't they,Ted?
那好, 准备好了吗?
So,what,we ready for tonight?
有件事我们得先做
Just one thing we got to do first.
来点吉姆・宾波本威酒?
Shot of Jim Beam?
耶!
Yes!
还有我答应Lily要装好200份邀请函
And then I promised Lily that we'd stuff
200 wedding invitations.
什么?!
What?!
抱歉, 伙计
I'm sorry,dude,
但你也看到她压力有多大拉
but you saw how stressed out she is.
拜托! 你一直不停的忙婚礼的事情
Come on! You've been doing wedding stuff nonstop.
休息下
Take a break.
一旦结婚
Once you're married,
如果你出门喝醉酒呕吐
if we go out and you get so drunk you throw up,
会很惨
it'll be sad,
但如果今晚这样...
but if we do it tonight...
会比结婚后好点
it'll be less sad.
好吧, 这样会很酷
Okay,it'll be cool
我来告诉你
I'll tell you what.
我们来玩个游戏
We'll make a game out of it.
首先把邀请函装好得到个大奖励
First one to stuff a hundred invitations
gets a big prize.
我看起来象才4岁吗?
Do I look like I'm four?
好吧, 你说的是什么奖励?
All right,what kind of prize are we talking?
比我们高中时候保安更多
a lot more security than when we were kids.
这样行吗?
Is this gonna work?
听着, 我17岁时
Look,when I was 17,
我经常溜进酒吧
I used to sneak into clubs all the time.
关键是要有自信
It's all about confidence.
跟着我
Follow me.
舞会快乐, 各位
Happy prom,everybody.
去舞会咯
Going to prom
你们是成人
you're adults.
好吧, 拜
Okay,bye.
好吧, 听着
Okay,look,
我只是想看看乐队
I just need to see the band.
我两个月内就要举行婚礼了, 但...
I'm getting married in two months,and...
那你现在才找乐队?
And you're just finding a band?
抱歉, 夫人
I'm sorry,ma'am.
必需得是学生或者学生的舞伴
You either need to be a student or the date of a student.
"夫人?"
"Ma'am?"
真失败
Check and mate.
很酷
It's cool.
该执行计划B了
Time to activate plan B.
Scherbotsky, 会用十字弩吗?
Scherbotsky,how comfortable are you with a crossbow?
Scherbotsky?
嘿, 伙计们
Hey,guys.
你们想带两个辣妹去舞会不?
Do you want to take two hot girls to prom?
我们没钱
We don't have that kind of money.
免费的
For free.
噢, 当然好!
Oh,hell yeah!
很好
Great.
我叫Robin, 这是我朋友Lily
I'm Robin,this is my friend Lily.
走吧?
Shall we?
当然
Sure.
我知道会实现的
I knew it would happen.
我梦到了
This is the dream.
噢, 嘿, 等等
Oh,hey,wait.
Barney要怎么进去?
How's Barney getting in?
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
我会进去的
I'll get in.
我们进来了!
we're in!
谢谢
Thank you.
我们休息片刻
We're going to take a break.
在开玩笑吧
you're kidding me.
女士们想来点跨越年龄的东西吗?
you ladies want something to take the edge off?
管他呢? 这可是是毕业舞会
what the hell?It's prom.
喝起来象止咳糖浆
that tastes like cough syrup.
我们弄不到酒精
we couldn't get any alcohol.
我们的假身份证上写的是20岁
our fake ids say we're only 20.
我们买回来才发现
We didn't realize it till after we bought them.
不擅长数学的书呆子?
Nerds who aren't good at math?
你们的未来很坎坷, 小伙子们
Life's going to be rough,boys.
嗨
Hi.
打扰
Excuse me.
不知道你们能不能演奏Violent Femmes的"good feeling"
I was wondering if you guys could play
"good feeling" by the Violent Femmes.
我知道这可能不在你们的节目单上
I know it's probably not in your repertoire,
但我快结婚了,我未婚夫想请你们在婚礼上演奏
but I'm getting married and my fiance
wants to hire you guys as the band,
但我没听过你们演奏"good feeling"就不能接受你们
but I can't sign off on it until I hear you play "good feeling"
因为这是我们的歌
because that's our song,
如果你们不能演奏我们的歌
and what kind of wedding band would you be
哪算婚礼乐队, 对吗?
if you couldn't play our song,right?
对吗?
Right?
听着, 我现在有点迷糊
Look,I'm kinda wasted right now,
听不懂你说什么
so I didn't understand any of that.
但如果你找来活页乐谱
But,if you get us the sheet music,
我们就演奏你的歌
we'll play your song.
有反应吗, 宝贝?
So,you buzzing,baby?
我的痰没了
My phlegm feels looser.
这太可悲了
This is pathetic.
现在是单身之夜
It's guys' night.
我们应该在酒吧里大打一场
We should be out in a bar getting in fights.
如果我打架, 你会帮我吗?
If I got in a fight,would you have my back?
当然
You know it.
我也会
I'd have your back,too.
这不错
That's cool.
什么, 你觉得不需要我帮助吗?
what,you don't think you'd need my help?
你不知道我多厉害
You don't know what I can do.
我就像...
I'm like...
像个狂暴战士
like a berserker.
好了, Ted
Okay,Ted.
喂
Hello.
嘿, 我是Robin
Hey,it's Robin.
Lily要你下载"good feeling"的活页乐谱
Lily needs you to download the sheet
music for "good feeling"
然后马上带过来
and bring it out here,like,now.
等等
Hang on.
是Robin
It's Robin.
她想让我去舞会
She wants me to go to prom.
Ted可以去吗?
Can Ted come?
等等! 别问!
Wait! Don't ask!
这太蹩脚了!
That's so lame!
我根本不想去
I don't even want to go anyway.
呃, 我不知道
Uh,I don't know.
现在我们两之间太怪异了
Things have been so weird between us.
她说什么?
What'd she say?
他撒谎说和女朋友分手
He lied and told me he broke up
with his girlfriend
来勾搭我
to try to hook up with me.
我是说, 我知道他道歉了
I mean,I know he apologized for it
但是很难原谅他
but it's just,it's not easy to forgive.
听着, 如果你一定要带Ted来
Look,if you absolutely must bring Ted,
我也不至于把自己眼珠挖出来
it's,it's not like I'm going to claw
my own eyes out if he comes.
好, 拜
Okay,bye.
她完全愿意你过去
She totally wants you to come.
好了, 活页乐谱在路上了
All right,sheet music's on the way.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
婚礼还有好多事情要筹备
There's just so much to do for this wedding.
我脑袋晕了
My head is swirling.
这些来的太快了
It's just all moving too fast.
怎么快了?
How is it moving too fast?
我们在一起两年拉
We've been together for two years.
我只是...
I just...
我只是不想人生每件事都被决定好
I just don't want everything in
my life to be decided already.
什么决定好了?
What's decided?
我去裁判学校
I go to umpire school,
你去念大学
you go to college.
我们搬进我爸爸斯塔腾岛上的房子
We move into my dad's house in Staten Island.
我们会有孩子, 我们一起变老
We have kids,we grow old together.
有什么决定好了?
What's decided?
充满变数的!
It's wide open!
Scooter
Scooter,
我去大学的时候
when I go off to college,
就是我们结束的时候
that's the end for us.
你要
You're,
你要和我分手吗?
you're breaking up with me?
还有很多我想做的事情
There's still so much I want to do.
我想去旅行
I want to travel,
做个海外艺术青年
live overseas as an artist,
也许来段同性恋情
maybe have a lesbian relationship.
另外, 我和你约会
Plus,I think I was just dating you
是因为你长有点象Kurt Cobain
(吞枪自杀的Nirvana主唱)
cause you look a little bit like Kurt Cobain.
我不敢相信这个
I can't believe this.
我可以改变
I can change.
我可以让自己更象Kurt Cobain
I can look more like Kurt Cobain.
拜托, 别离开我
Please,just don't leave me.
除了你我什么都没有了, 宝贝
I'm nothing without you,baby.
拜托别给我这么大压力!
Please don't put that kind of pressure on me!
这太多了!
It's too much!
只是一支舞, 天那!
It's just one dance,god!
什么?
What?
我们答应他们跳支舞的
we did promise them one dance.
当然可以
sure,okay.
那么Andrew
so Andrew,
你的人生大计是什么?
what's your big plan?
今晚之后生活将怎样安排?
What's life going to be like after tonight?
我把一切都安排好了
you know I got it all worked out.
头也不回地离开这个地方
leave this place in my dust,
大学四年的精彩生活
four awesome years at college,
然后我会搬去布拉格
and then I'll move to prague
或者开办我自己的游戏公司或其他什么
or start my own video game company or something.
不, 你不会
No,you won't.
我不会?
I won't?
对, 你不会达成你设想的任何事
No,you won't accomplish anything you set out to.
你会在大学第一天交个女朋友
You'll get a girlfriend the first day of college
然后你放弃独立
and you'll give up your independence
然后你永远不会住在国外
and you'll never live abroad
你会在思考"我的希望和梦想呢?"
and you'll wind up old before your time wondering
前慢慢变老
"whatever happened to my hopes and my dreams?"
你真觉得我会找到个女朋友吗?
You really think i'll get a girlfriend?
是为了什么?
So what's the deal here?
我今晚走运了吗?
Am I getting lucky tonight?
Sean, 听着
Sean,look,
你是个好人
you're a nice guy,
但是我只是...
but I just don't...
不, 你今晚不会走运
no,you're not getting lucky tonight.
好了, 酷一点
Okay,just be cool.
别看着我
Don't look at me.
好的
Okay.
你们怎么进来的?
How'd you get in here?
怎么了你
What's it to you,
巨型海龟?
giant turtle?
是我, Barney
It's me,Barney.
Lily呢?
Where's Lily?
她去洗手间了
She's in the bathroom.
等在这, 我得去找下乐队
Wait here,I should go talk to the band.
好
All right.
你们两个家伙怎么进来的?
How did you guys get in here?
我们从后面进来的
We just snuck in the back.
你们...
You just snu...
真的吗?
are you serious?
我整晚都在试着溜进来
I've been trying to get in here all night.
最后好不容易才给了看门人200块钱
让我借了这套吉祥物制服
I finally paid a janitor 200 bucks
to let me borrow this mascot costume.
但你还是进来了
But you got in.
又慢又稳的赢得了赛跑
slow and steady won the race.
嘿, 兄弟
Hey,bro,
你们有看见我的未婚妻Lily吗?
have you seen my fiancee Lily?
你未婚妻?
Your fiancee?
今晚她是我的伴, 兄弟
tonight she's with me,bro.
除非你想找茬
Unless you're looking for trouble.
听着, 小家伙
Listen,little buddy,
我知道这是毕业舞会
I understand it's prom
肾上腺素增长, 但...
and the adrenaline's pumping,but...
不, 不是今晚
no,not tonight.
我等待这刻很久了
I've waited too long for this.
我终于找到了个女孩
I finally got a girl
我不会让你把她从我旁边带走的
and I'm not going to let you take
her away from me.
听着, 不是带走
Look,let's not get carried away.
呀! 双节棍!
Yah! Nunchaku!
我不敢相信我对个高中生那样
I can't believe I unloaded like that
on a high school senior.
我不敢相信一个高中生对我那样
I can't believe a high school senior
unloaded like that on me.
我要问你个问题
I'm going to ask you something
也许这很疯狂
and,maybe it's crazy
因为你们永远是最可爱的一对
cause you guys are the cutest couple ever.
但, 呃
But,um
你犹豫了吗?
are you having second thoughts?
嗯,但不是因为Marshall
But not about Marshall.
是我自己
About me.
我不停的想着十年前的自己
I just keep thinking about the girl
I was ten years ago
想着她经历了什么
and wondering what happened to her.
我不想被绑死在一个地方
I don't want to be tied down.
我想游居于法国, 西班牙和意大利
I want to live in France and Spain and Italy
汲取生活
and just soak up life
然后画在画布上
and put it on a canvas,
就算得在烂咖啡馆里端上五年盘子
even if it means being a waitress
in crappy cafee for five years,
我也不在乎
I don't care.
我要当个画家
I'm going to be a painter.
旁边有个男朋友牵着我脖子
And I can't do any of that with a,
我就做不了这些了, 你懂吗?
with a boyfriend shackled
around my neck,you know?
但无论如何, 我话多
But anyway,I'm blabbering.
交朋友的方式, Lily
Way to make new friends,Lily.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
能再说次你的名字吗?
What was your name again?
Marshall
Marshall.
很高兴认识你, Marshall
Nice to meet you,Marshall.
我们住对门
Guess we're hallmates.
装好了
it works.
Violent Femmes的
Violent Femmes.
我喜欢这首歌
I love this song.
我也是
Me,too.
我的人生计划一件都没实现
I didn't have any of the experiences I set out to.
旅行
The travel,
波希米亚艺术生活
the Bohemian art life,
我的盛大同性恋经历
my big lesbian experience.
我什么也没做
I didn't do any of it.
Lily
Lily,
你要和世界上你最好的朋友结婚了
you're marrying your best friend in the world.
这难道不值得用所有这些经历换取吗?
I mean,isn't that worth all the other
experiences combined?
还有, 你还是可以旅行
And look,you can still travel,
还是可以绘画
I mean,you can still paint.
至于你的同性恋经历...
And as far as your lesbian experience...
开心了不?
happy?
现在欲火中烧了吧?
So felt hotty?
闭嘴
Shut up.
非法入侵, 袭击未成年人
Trespassing,assaulting a minor.
你偷的这套吉祥物制服价值5,000元
This mascot costume you stole cost $5,000.
我们可以逮捕你们, 知道吗?
We can have you guys arrested,you know that?
噢, 拜托
Oh,come on
你让孩子带着双节棍进去
you're the one who let in a kid with nunchakus.
你们称的上保全人员吗?
You call yourself security guards?
我只是在保护我的男孩
I was just defending my boy here.
我完全可以搞定那个小孩
I totally could have taken that kid.
我也完全帮你了, 所以...
and I totally had your back,so...
嗯, 我不需要
well,I don't need it,
但谢谢
but thanks.
耶, 你需要, 不用谢
yeah,you did,and you're welcome.
不, 那个孩子估计
No,the kid was totally,like,
也就是个白带, 而我那么高大
a white belt and I'm gigantic.
听着, 伙计们, 我很抱歉
Listen,guys,I'm sorry.
拜托, 我只要进去再听一首歌就可以了
Please,I just need to get in there
for one more song.
不可能
Absolutely not.
你们稍后再感谢我, 好吗?
You guys will thank me for this later,okay?
听着, Don, Ray
Listen,Don,Ray,
我们可以...?
can't we all...?
你知道, 作为乌龟
You know,for a turtle,
他跑的惊人的快
he's surprisingly quick.
这首歌献给那位红发女士和高个男士
This one goes out to that redhead
girl and that tall guy.
*Good feeling
Good feeling,
*won't you stay with me just a little longer?
won't you stay with me just a little longer?
*It always seems like you're leaving
It always seems like you're leaving
*when I need you here just a little longer
when I need you here just a little longer
你的第一个毕业舞会怎么样?
so how was your first prom?
你告诉我
You tell me.
我讨厌我的礼服
I hated my dress,
我的舞伴吐在我身上
my date got wasted and puked on me,
发生了打斗事件还有我吻了个女孩
there was a huge fight and I kissed a girl.
那么, 基本上
So,basically,
确实是毕业舞会
it was a prom.
好吧, 我有想你
Okay,I've missed you.
不是因为理解
Not in a we're-going-to-make-out way,
不是因为我原谅你
not even in an I-forgive-you way.
只是我很想你
Just in a I've-missed-you way.
我还奢望别的什么呢？
what I can get?
我的朋友们
And that,my friends,
所以说穿着牛仔装去看脱衣舞很吃亏
is why you don't get your money's worth when you wear jeans to a strip club.
所以你得同意
So you got to admit,
88乐队在摇滚我们的歌
the 88 are rocking our song.
不错
it's good.
乐队?
Band?
搞定
Check.
两个月, 宝贝
Two months,baby.
两个月
Two months.
--------------------------
本字幕由cece&飞飞字幕组倾情奉献
LOVE-==cece&飞飞==-LOVE
--------------------------
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-
制作: 飞飞
校对: cece
-==LOVE==-
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第一季第二十集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
Season 01 Episode 20